showbizspy.com 2019-04-11

# PRIVACY ⋆ SHOWBIZ SPY

This privacy statement covers Showbiz Spy:

Information Collection

Showbiz Spy may collect information from our users at different points on the site. Showbiz Spy is the sole owner of the information collected on ShowbizSpy.com.

Comments and Posts

Showbiz Spy users can choose to write comments or posts on the site. To leave a comment, users must submit a valid e-mail address. Showbiz Spy uses this information to screen out users who leave comments that violate our terms and conditions of use. Showbiz Spy does not share user information with any other organization.

Newsletters

Showbiz Spy offers e-mail newsletters. Users who subscribe to the Showbiz Spy newsletter will receive regular email updates about new content and features.

To sign up to receive regular e-mails, users must submit information including a valid e-mail address. Showbiz Spy does not share contact or personal information with any other organization.

This information can be used in aggregate form to assess general user interest in various internal and third-party products and services, and your personal and contact information will not be passed to any other organization. Users who choose to sign up for a mailing list will receive regular e-mails, including new articles added to the site.

Showbiz Spy may periodically e-mail you messages about products and services that we think may be of interest to you. We may also produce contests, sweepstakes and special events with the support of promotional partners. Information collected by our Sites in conjunction with such events may also be used for the marketing of additional services and events by the Sites and/or their promotional partners. In the instance that there is a conflict between this privacy policy and the rules or policies applicable to a special event, the rules and policies associated with the special event shall govern. You can choose not to receive such messages in the future by following the “unsubscribe” instructions located near the bottom of each e-mail.

Cookies

Showbiz Spy may use cookies. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer, tied to information about the user. We may use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. Session ID cookies terminate as soon as the user closes his or her browser. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user’s hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help instructions.

Third-Party Cookies

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads and collect information when you visit Showbiz Spy. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Third-party advertisers’ use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies. Showbiz Spy has no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.

Log Files

Like most websites, our servers use log files. These log files record include Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks. Showbiz Spy uses this information to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. Showbiz Spy may use a tracking utility that uses log files to analyze user movement.

Legal Disclaimer

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, Showbiz Spy may need to disclose personal information when required by law, wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process.

Business Transitions

In the event Showbiz Spy goes through a business transition such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of a portion of its assets, users’ personal information may be part of the assets transferred.

Links

Showbiz Spy publishes links to other sites. Please be aware that Showbiz Spy is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site, and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Showbiz Spy.

Third-Party Cookies

Some of our business partners (i.e. advertisers), may use cookies on our site. Showbiz Spy has no access to or control over these cookies once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Showbiz Spy only, and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

Third-Party Advertising

The advertisements appearing on this website are delivered to users by Google, among other services. Information about a user’s visit to showbizspy.com, such as the number of times they have viewed an advertisement (but not username, date of birth, or any other personal information), is used to serve ads to users on this site.

Information Collected Through Third-Party Sources

This type of information is collected anonymously by approved third-party partners (such as online marketing firms, research companies, social media companies, ad targeting firms, and other partners). None of the information collected by these sources contains any personally identifying information. This type of information includes but is not limited to:

Demographic information (gender, age, HHI, job title, interests, etc.)  
Advertising information (clicks, interactions, post-impression performance data)  
Social networking information (Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, etc.)  
Research information (data collected from partners)

Notification of Changes

Whenever Showbiz Spy changes its privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, and other places we deem appropriate.

Contact Information

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.
